Muhammet Wael Akkash

Turkey | +90 534 270 8183 | muhammetakkas860@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammetakkas/

EDUCATION

Nisantasi Unversite Turkey. istanbul

Software Engineer Graduation Date: May 2024

SUMMARY

Summary: Experience in programming languages (Java • C# • Html • Css • JavaScript • React.Js • Node,Js • WordPrees) and creating websites, programs and applications that suit all operating systems according to modern strategies and flexible methods that suit modification in all cases

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Skills: Website programming • Create web pages • Create phone applications.Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint) Project Management • Facebook Ads • Instagram Advertising • Paid Media Advertising • Paid Social Media Advertising • Search Advertising • Business Strategy • Strategic Partnerships • Marketing Management

WORK EXPERIENCE

Arı bilgi bilişim teknolojileri akademisi

İstanbul

internship

May 2024 - Aug 2024

As a computer engineering student, I am dedicated to continuously improving my skills in software
development and web technologies. During my internships, I gained hands-on experience in web
application development, backend technologies, and database management. I also had the opportunity
to work on RESTful API integration and design performance-oriented systems

Automata4 Group İstanbul

experience Mar 2022 - Jan 2023

- Online training, starting to create websites, and receiving job assignments
- Working on creating websites and systems to facilitate student affairs and services at universities.

Stellar Property İstanbul

Web Administrato Feb 2023 - Jul 2024

- · Website and upload manager
- · Chief web office

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

GitHub İstanbul

https://github.com/Muhammetakks

- MyProfile(<u>https://muhammet-gamma.vercel.app</u>)
- RentCar (https://github.com/Muhammetakks/RentaCar)
- ShoeStore (https://github.com/Muhammetakks/ShoeStore)
- ChefWeb (https://github.com/Muhammetakks/ChefWeb)
- TravelSphere (https://github.com/Muhammetakks/TravelSphere)
- Fitnees (https://github.com/Muhammetakks/Fitness)